One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Open up the borderless map, then
‫استهل قراءة الخريطة التي لا حدود لها‬
Head for that unknown edge of the ocean
‫انطلق نحو المكان الذي لا نهاية له‬
LET’S SAIL ON right now, hoist your sails up high
‫لنبحر للأمام ونرفع تلك الأشرعة‬
Riding on the wind
‫الحق بالرياح‬
DON’T GIVE UP, it’s time to finish what we started
‫لا تستسلم ما دمت عازمًا‬
So don't you grow disheartened
‫فلا عودة للوراء‬
Laugh the tears away through the storm
‫سنواجه المياه المتقلبة بضحكاتنا‬
SHOUT IT OUT, when you feel down always remember
‫اصرخ لحماية عزيمتك من الانكسار‬
That’s what your friends are there for
‫فرفاقك يقفون إلى جانبك‬
Y’know there’s no point in fronting,
‫ليس عليك التظاهر بالقوة أبدًا‬
Even in the face of utter darkness
‫ولو حاولت الظلمة أن تنال من صميمك‬
C’mon, BRAVE IT OUT We’ll be alright
‫هيا، تشجع‬
Together you know that we’ll never lose a fight
‫فالروابط الثابتة باقية‬
Open up the borderless map, then
‫استهل قراءة الخريطة التي لا حدود لها‬
Head for that unknown edge of the ocean
‫انطلق نحو المكان الذي لا نهاية له‬
All great journeys starts with a single step
‫كن جسورًا لتخطو خطوة للأمام‬
DREAMIN’ ON
‫تمسّك بالحُلم‬
Open up the borderless map, then
‫استهل قراءة الخريطة التي لا حدود لها‬
Raise the flag we swore to defend
‫تلك الراية برهان على نذرنا‬
We’ll never stop until we’ve reached the top
‫تواصل النضال‬
Just be true to yourself until the end
‫فابقَ مخلصًا لجوهرك‬
Set sail and grab it, DREAMIN ON
‫تمسك بالحلم وداوم عليه‬
My Bible
‫كتابي المبجل‬
Big Sis! Stay with me!
‫تماسكي يا أختاه‬
Big Sis!
‫أختاه!‬
Hey, dumbasses!
‫أيها الأراذل، استدعوا الطاقم الطبي حالًا!‬
Hey!
‫هيا!‬
Sir!
‫حاضر‬
Find those two, corner them, then summon the rest of us.
‫لا تفقدا أثرهما، أبقوهما محاصرَيْن وأبلغونا مكانهما‬
Yamato, you bastard...
‫الوغد ياماتو...‬
Page One!
‫يبدو أنك تلقيت ضررًا بالغًا أيضًا يا بيج ون-سان‬
Yeah, that was quite the punch...
‫كانت تلك ضربة قوية فعلًا، محتملٌ أن فكي خُلع من مكانه‬
That's all?!
‫أهذا فحسب؟!‬
More importantly, where are the medics?
‫الأهم من ذلك، ألم يصل الطاقم الطبي بعد؟‬
We're here!
‫وصلنا‬
You're hurting my eyes!
‫أنت تؤذي عيني‬
Pay-Pay!
‫باي-تان!‬
It hurts ever so much!
‫آلمني ذلك-أرينسو، وا أسفاه على حالي!‬
Maybe you should pipe down then?
‫لمَ لا تهدئين أعصابك إذًا؟‬
What did you say?!
‫«تهدئين»؟‬
Are you trying to make me cry?!
‫لا تُبكِ أختك يا هذا!‬
That lousy Yamato!
‫كما أن ذاك الوغد ياماتو...‬
How dare he steal Viceroy Kaido's Thunder Bagua?!
‫كيف له أن يسرق هجمة كايدو-ساما «قصف الرعد ثماني المسارات»؟!‬
She's fine all right.
‫أراكِ بخير حال‬
His is more like Blunder Bagua.
‫الأجدر تسميتها «قصف الرعد رباعي المسارات»‬
It didn't even hurt...
‫لم تؤلمني مطلقًا...‬
Big Sis...
‫أختاه...‬
Master Page One!
‫يا بيج ون-ساما، توقف ياماتو-ساما وقبعة القش‬
Okay!
‫حسنٌ‬
Hey, Pay-Pay!
‫يا باي-تان‬
Don't leave me!
‫لا تتركني!‬
Where are you taking me?!
‫إلى أين تصحبني؟ لستُ متفرغًا لغُرباء!‬
Please wait.
‫على مهلك، أودّ محادثتك فحسب‬
Get out of my way!
‫ابتعد عن طريقي‬
Listen to what I have to say!
‫أنصت لما أود قوله‬
You have five seconds!
‫أمامك خمس ثوانٍ‬
People can hear us.
‫يمكن للناس سماعنا هنا، أودّ محادثتك بسريَّة‬
Then forget it!
‫أرفض إذًا‬
Gum-Gum...
‫فاكهة المطاط‬
Gatling!
‫الرشاش‬
You stubborn jerk!
‫أنت صعب المراس‬
Red Hawk!
‫الصقر الأحمر‬
This reminds me of...
‫هذا يذكرني...‬
my battle against him!
‫بقتالي معه...‬
Damn!
‫سُحقًا، قد هربا‬
What's going on?
‫ماذا يحدث هنا؟ أين ياماتو؟‬
I'm sorry!
‫نعتذر، فقدنا أثريهما‬
Performance Floor Skull Dome
‫طابق العرض المباشر‬ ‫قبة الجمجمة‬
The day Kozuki Oden fell...
‫في يوم مصرع أودين،‬
his stronghold, Oden Castle, fell alongside him!
‫تهدَّم مقر حكمه قلعة أودين أيضًا!‬
However, a group of people inside the castle vanished into thin air!
‫لكن عدّةَ أشخاصٍ كانوا داخل قلعته اختفوا دون أثر‬
Samurai from the Red Scabbards and this runt!
‫وإنهم ساموراي الأغماد وهذا الطفل!‬
Where did they disappear to?
‫أين هربوا يا تُرى؟!‬
To the future!
‫إلى المستقبل!‬
They crossed through twenty years of time...
‫عبروا عشرين عامًا من الزمن!‬
resurfacing in the Wano of today! They haven't aged a day!
‫وظهروا في حاضر بلاد وانو كما كانوا عليه حينها!‬
And who exactly was responsible for this sorcery?!
‫من مسؤول تلك الشعوذة يا تُرى؟!‬
I'll tell you...
‫سأخبركم!‬
None other than Kozuki Toki!
‫اسمها كوزكي توكي!‬
Oden's wife, Toki, was a witch who could send these malcontents into the future!
‫أرسلت توكي زوجة أودين ضغينتها إلى المستقبل، إنها لمشعوذة!‬
No way!
‫يصعب تصديق ذلك‬
There are brats with topknots all over Wano!
‫هنالك أطفال كُثر يعقدون شعر رأسهم للأعلى مثله في بلاد وانو‬
The Kozuki name died out decades ago!
‫انقرضت عشيرة الكوزكي منذ أمدٍ بعيد‬
Right, brother?!
‫ألست مُحقًّا يا شقيقي؟‬
Yeah, man!
‫فعلًا!‬
Y-You're totally right!
‫كـ-كلامك عين الصواب!‬
Yo, yo, Shogun Orochi!
‫يا أوروتشي-ساما،‬
Don't keep him so far from us!
‫لا يمكننا رؤيته من مسافة بعيدة!‬
Bring that brat down here!
‫اجلبوه إليّ لأفقأ عينيه‬
How dare you call my mother a witch?!
‫ما كانت أمي بالمشعوذة،‬
Y-You will pay for that, Orochi!
‫لـ-لن أغفر لك يا أوروتشي!‬
Insolent whelp! Don't try to act tough!
‫أتتظاهر بالحزم أيها الشقي؟!‬
How should I execute you?!
‫كيف أُعدمك يا تُرى؟‬
Impalement?
‫بالطعن؟‬
Shooting?
‫أم رميك بالرصاص؟‬
Or maybe boiling?!
‫أم أغليك حيًّا؟‬
What should we do, Boss?
‫كيف نتصرف يا حضرة الزعيم؟‬
I can't stand watching Momo like this!
‫لا أحتمل رؤية مومو-تشان بتلك الحالة‬
The samurai will surely act.
‫سيتصرف الساموراي بالتأكيد‬
Hold fast, Nico Robin!
‫علينا التريث يا نيكو روبين‬
Lord Momonosuke!
‫مومونوسكي-ساما!‬
Though frustrated by their inability to rescue Momonosuke,
‫رغم يأسهم من محاولة إنقاذ مومونوسكي،‬
the raiding forces have successfully blended into the banquet!
‫نجح جنود الغارة في التسلل داخل المأدبة‬
Meanwhile, Law's submarine, the Polar Tang, which was carrying the Red Scabbards samurai,
‫أثناء ذلك، غواصة لاو البولر تانغ التي تحمل على متنها ساموراي الأغماد‬
Law
‫لاو‬
LawLaw
‫لاولاو‬
reached the back of the island.
‫أوصلتهم إلى مدخل الجزيرة الخلفي‬
Law
‫لاو‬
Adjust trim, 38 degrees!
‫ضبط التوازن 38 درجة!‬
Adjusting, 38 degrees!
‫التوازن 38 درجة!‬
Get as close to the island as possible!
‫اقترب من الجزيرة قدر المستطاع‬
Yes, sir!
‫عُلم‬
Strong currents are forming all around us!
‫يمتد تيار قوي في مساحة واسعة‬
It's the same up there.
‫الأمر سيان في الأعلى، لا فرصة لنا سوى واحدة حالما نطفو على السطح‬
Understood!
‫مفهوم‬
We're counting on you, Traffy!
‫سنكون في رعايتك يا تراو-سان‬
Bepo! Shachi! Penguin!
‫هل أنتم جاهزون يا بيبو وشاتشي وبينغين؟‬
Aye, aye, Captain!
‫أجل يا قبطان!‬
– Aye, aye, sir!
‫أجل يا سيدي!‬
We're coming for you, Kaido!
‫هدفنا هو كايدو!‬
All systems clear!
‫جميع الأنظمة سليمة، يُصرح بالطفو‬
Alright! Surface!
‫حسنٌ، اطفوا‬
It's snowing...?
‫ثلج؟‬
Room!
‫المجال‬
Shambles!
‫البعثرة‬
They're gone!
‫رحلوا‬
Close the door!
‫أغلقوا الباب، سنغطس ثانيةً‬
Roger!
‫عُلم!‬
Rapid descent!
‫نزول سريع!‬
We're here!
‫وصلنا‬
That technique of yours is remarkable!
‫لمذهلةٌ التقنية التي استخدمتها‬
There are two entrances.
‫ثمة مدخلان،‬
No doubt Kaido will be up there.
‫الوصول لكايدو سيكون من المدخل العلوي بلا شك‬
Hey!
‫على رسلك، لمَ الشدة؟‬
You're asking too much!
‫كفاك شكوى، فهذه فكرتك العظيمة-يوي‬
Hey, wait!
‫مهلًا، انتظر...‬
That must be...
‫هذا الصوت...‬
Ow, ow, ow...
‫مؤلم، مؤلم‬
Come on, mew need to be careful!
‫كان ذلك لئيمًا‬
Nekomamushi!
‫نيكوماموشي!‬
You have grown much bigger!
‫بُتَّ ضخمًا!‬
Kawamatsu! You're alive!
‫ما زلت حيًّا إذًا يا كاواماتسو!‬
Ashura!
‫أشورا!‬
You made it too!
‫أشورا هنا أيضًا‬
Yeah, it's been a while!
‫بلى، طالت بيننا المهاجر‬
Marco! You carried him here?!
‫هل حملته إلى هنا يا ماركو؟‬
Carrying two people really takes it out of you!
‫حمل كليهما أرهقني وأتعبني حقًّا‬
Two?!
‫كليهما؟‬
– Izo!
‫إيزو!‬
Big Brother...
‫أخي الأكبر...‬
Big Brother!
‫أخي الأكبر!‬
Kiku, you have become a fine samurai.
‫أصبحت ساموراي عظيم يا كيكو‬
– Izo!
‫إيزو!‬
You are a sight for sore eyes!
‫هذا يبعث على الارتياح!‬
I am so glad that you came back!
‫يسرني تمكنك من العودة!‬
I forgot to mention it before!
‫لم أطلعكم أنه قادم‬
Marco said he knew Izo's whereabouts, so I went there to see him!
‫قال ماركو إنه يعرف مكان إيزو لذا ذهبت لأحضره‬
Marco! You haven't changed one bit!
‫لم تتغير قط يا ماركو‬
You think?
‫حقًّا؟‬
We can reminisce about the good old days later!
‫لنستذكر الماضي لاحقًا‬
Something on the sea caught my eye earlier, so I'm gonna go check it out.
‫رأيت شيئًا مريبًا في البحر قبل قليل، سأتقصى أمره‬
Marco! Thank you!
‫شكرًا يا ماركو‬
I'm glad I waited for twenty years.
‫انتظرت عشرين عامًا طِوَالَ من أجل هذا!‬
Let's take down Kaido at any cost!
‫لنسقط كايدو بأي ثمن!‬
Hey, is Linlin ready yet?!
‫ألم تنتهِ لينلين بعد؟‬
You should've told me that, Bao Huang!
‫لمَ لمْ تُخبريني بهذا مُسبقًا يا باو هان؟‬
My bad!
‫المعذرة‬
You can go now.
‫لا يهم‬
We'll make our grand announcement alongside Momonosuke's execution!
‫سأُقدِّم إعلاني الضخم خلال إعدام مومونوسكي‬
Let's go!
‫هيّا بنا‬
All right!
‫هيّا، لنشرب الساكي احتفالًا بتنفيذ حكم الإعدام!‬
Here comes Viceroy Kaido!
‫ظهر كايدو-ساما!‬
Listen up!
‫أنصتوا...‬
All you bastards!
‫أيها الجمع!‬
Allow me to spice up this brat's dull execution.
‫لننعش مراسم الإعدام المملة هذه بأمرٍ مشوق‬
This is... the New Onigashima Project!
‫مبادرة أونيغاشيما الجديدة!‬
Castle Attic
‫عُلية‬ ‫القلعة‬
Five minutes!
‫معك خمس دقائق‬
Years ago...
‫ذات يومٍ،‬
I told my father...
‫أخبرتُ أبي...‬
that I wanted to become Kozuki Oden.
‫أني أريد أن أصبح كوزكي أودين...‬
In return, he disciplined me thoroughly.
‫فضربني أبي ضربًا مبرحًا‬
Why are you telling me this?!
‫وما غايتك بإخباري هذا؟‬
And why now of all times?!
‫ولمَ الآن تحديدًا؟!‬
Twenty years ago, I witnessed Oden's execution...
‫رأيتُ ساعة إعدام أودين الأسطورية قبل عشرين عامًا‬
As a samurai, he was peerless.
‫لم يكن هنالك ساموراي على شاكلته،‬
The ones who killed him...
‫ومن قتلاه...‬
were Orochi and my father...
‫كانا أوروتشي ومعه أبي......‬
Kaido!
‫كايدو...!‬
It was infuriating...!
‫كان ذلك مُحبطًا‬
Yet, above all,
‫الأهم من ذلك،‬
my heart was stirred. My tears flowed freely!
‫تأثرت بشدة وانهمرت دموعي‬
Later, I found this in Kuri.
‫وبعدها عثرتُ على هذا في كوري...‬
"Oden's Travel Record"
‫سـجـل رحـلات أوديـن‬
Kozuki Oden's logbook.
‫سجل رحلات كوزكي أودين!‬
Oh, his journal!
‫إنها مذكراته!‬
It's my bible!
‫إنه كتابي المبجل‬
Not even my father or his crew know about this journal!
‫لا يعرف أبي والآخرون عن وجود هذه المذكرات‬
The pages are filled with his heroic tales and other important tidbits.
‫مآثره البطولية وغيرها من الحكايات الجسيمة مُدوَّنة هنا‬
Now that the Red Scabbards are dead,
‫وبما أن ساموراي الأغماد موتى،‬
someone has to inherit Oden's will!
‫كان لزامًا أن يحمل أحد إرادة أودين‬
That's why...
‫ولهذا أنا...‬
I'm going to open up this country!
‫سأفتح هذه البلاد!‬
You're...
‫أنت...‬
Allow me to fight alongside you!
‫سأقاتل إلى جانبك‬
You said you were Kaido's son.
‫ألم تقل إنك «ابن» كايدو؟‬
Kozuki Oden was a man, correct?
‫ألم يكن كوزكي أودين رجلًا؟‬
So I became a man, too.
‫توضيح: ياماتو ليست متحولةً جنسيًّا لكنها تُخاطب وتتكلم بضمير المذكر‬
You are incredibly strong.
‫أنت شديد البأس‬
I could tell you were holding back when we fought before.
‫لم تكن جادًا في قتالنا قبلًا، صحيح؟‬
You remind me of Ace.
‫تُذكرني بإيس‬
Huh?!
‫ماذا؟!‬
Kaido's Daughter
‫ابنة كايدو‬
(Self-Proclaimed Kozuki Oden)
‫(تدّعي أنها كوزكي أودين)‬
Yam
‫يا‬
Ya
‫ما‬
Y a Kaido's Daughter m
‫ياتو‬
ato
‫ياما‬
Yama
‫تو‬
Rear Entrance
‫المدخل‬ ‫الخلفي‬
I knew you would come...
‫كنتُ في انتظاركم...‬
There was no trace of a samurai invasion...
‫فرغم أننا لم نلمح متسللين من الساموراي،‬
but I knew deep down that you could never stay away.
‫لكن يصعب التصديق أنكم لن تأتوا إلى هنا‬
I know your tenacity better than anyone!
‫فأنا أكثر الناس علمًا بعنادكم!‬
They're really here!
‫أتيتم حقًّا‬
After hiding like rats for twenty years since the boiling!
‫رأيتهم قبل عشرين عامًا في ذلك القدر المغلي‬
Kanjuro...
‫كنجورو...‬
Have you betrayed us?!
‫أخنتنا؟!‬
Your raid ends right here.
‫سأحبط غارتكم‬
Izo, you have returned... just to fight this losing battle?
‫أعُدتَ حتى تقاتل في هذه المعركة البائسة يا إيزو؟‬
They're decapitated, yet still able to fight...
‫محاربون بلا رؤوس يمكنهم القتال...‬
Nicely drawn.
‫يا لبراعة رسمك‬
They look just like you guys, don't they?!
‫ألا يشبهونكم؟‬
With Oden, you lost your head, and yet the body of the samurai writhes on.
‫حتى بعد أن فقدتم رؤوسكم مع أودين، ما زلتم تتلوون كالديْدَان‬
We still have our head!
‫لم نفقد رؤوسنا!‬
Our lord is Momonosuke!
‫فَوَليُّنَا هو مومونوسكي-ساما!‬
Is Lord Momonosuke okay?!
‫هل مومونوسكي-ساما بخير؟‬
I cannot say for certain...
‫لا يمكنني تأكيد ذلك‬
He was trying the best he could to escape.
‫بذل ما بوسعه ليحاول الفرار مني‬
How can I get to Lord Orochi?!
‫كيف أصل أوروتشي-ساما بسرعة؟‬
Halt!
‫انتظر!‬
I refuse to remain a burden to them!
‫لن أكون عبئًا على أحدٍ!‬
What are you doing?
‫ما الذي تفعله؟‬
If I let you get away...
‫إن هربت مني،‬
then I cannot fulfill my role!
‫فلن أتمكن من إتمام تأدية دوري‬
I only intended to knock him out...
‫كنت لأكتفي بإفقاده وعيه،‬
but I overdid it a little...
‫ولكني بالغت قليلًا...‬
Luckily, he clung on to life,
‫ولكن بفضل تمسكه المستميت بالحياة،‬
so I was able to hand him over to Lord Orochi.
‫تمكنت من تسليمه سالمًا إلى أوروتشي-ساما‬
Lord Momonosuke!
‫مومونوسكي-ساما!‬
Any minute now, Momonosuke will be executed on stage for all to see!
‫سيُنفَّذ الإعدام العلني في حقِّ مومونوسكي على المسرح بالداخل‬
All we have to do is stop you right here.
‫ولا علينا إلا اعاقتكم قليلًا‬
Minutes from now, the history of the Kozuki clan will come to an end.
‫سينتهي تاريخ الكوزكي بعد بضع دقائق‬
Don't mess with us, Kanjuro!
‫لا تقلل من شأننا يا كنجورو!‬
Advance!
‫هجوم!‬
Kappa Style:
‫أسلوب الكابا‬
Yorikiri!
‫القاطع المندفع للأمام‬
Flower Shuriken!
‫زهور الشوريكين‬
Go to hell!
‫اهلك!‬
You-gara! What happened to your leg?!
‫ما خطب ساقك؟‬
It's my two-sword style!
‫إنه أسلوب السيفين، أليسَ رائعًا؟‬
It's purrific!
‫فعلًا‬
Now what is that?
‫وما هذا؟‬
Isn't it cool?
‫أليسَ رائعًا؟‬
This will tear Kaido to shreds!
‫سيغربل كايدو بالرصاص‬
Cool...
‫رائع‬
What's wrong, Kiku?
‫ما الخطب يا كيكو؟‬
More... Cry some more!
‫لتنهمر... لتنهمر دموعك أكثر!‬
Come on...
‫هيا...‬
Come on!
‫هيا!‬
Please cease your drivel, Kanjuro.
‫أطبق فاهك يا كنجورو-سان.‬
To me, Kanjuro of the Evening Shower...
‫فإن وابل المساء كنجورو بالنسبة إليّ...‬
was a precious friend.
‫كان رفيقًا عزيزًا...‬
Prepare yourself.
‫تحضَّر جيدًا‬
The wounds from this blade shall follow you to your grave.
‫فإن الجروح التي يُحدثها نصل سيفي تتبعك إلى العالم الآخر‬
Kikunojo of the Lingering Snow A Retainer of the Kozuki Clan
‫كيكونوجو الثلج المتساقط‬ ‫من خدم عشيرة الكوزكي‬
Like the snow that remains in spring, so, too, shall they torment your soul forevermore!
‫ستعذب روحك إلى الأبد كبقايا الثلج في الربيع!‬
Come at me, Kiku!
‫تقدم يا كيكو!‬
Hey! Turn on the video transponder snail already!
‫هيا، ألم تشغلوا حلزون البث المرئي بعد؟‬
Kaido's speech has started!
‫بدأ خطاب كايدو-سان!‬
I, as Kozuki Oden, thought that you...
‫بصفتي كوزكي أودين...‬
as Ace's brother, would allow me to board your ship, so I gathered info on you.
‫توسمت فيك يا أخ إيس الأصغر لأن تصحبني على متن سفينتك نظير المعلومات التي جمعتها لك‬
Hey!
‫كوزكي أودين يتمتع بإعجاب الجميع لعلمك‬
You can't just be him!
‫فلن يمكنك أن تصبحي أودين فجأة‬
Fine, you're more Oden than I am!
‫أعرف أنك أشبه بأودين مني‬
What do you mean I'm more Oden than you?!
‫ما وجه الشبه بيني وبين أودين؟!‬
Even if I am Oden, I'm still not free...
‫رغم أني أودين لكني لستُ حرًّا‬
because of these cuffs!
‫وهذا بسبب هذه الأصفاد‬
I wanted to set out to sea along with Ace and his crew...
‫أردتُ الإبحار برفقة إيس في عرض البحر...‬
but I've been held captive on this island since I was eight!
‫كنتُ مجبورًا على البقاء في هذه الجزيرة منذ الثامنة من عمري‬
Aren't those for prisoners?
‫ألا تُسلسِل هذه المساجين؟‬
Yes!
‫أصبت، ذكر أبي أنها ستنفجر إن غادرت الجزيرة‬
Honestly, I think that was probably a lie...
‫بصراحة، أظنه يخادعني...‬
because what kind of a parent would blow up their own son?!
‫فأي والد هذا الذي قد يفجر بنته؟‬
But when I think of the worst case scenario, I feel weak at the knees...
‫لكن بأخذي حدوث الأسوأ في الحسبان ينتابني الضعف...‬
because my father is that kind of man.
‫فهذه من شيمة والدي‬
Want me to take them off?
‫أتُريد أن أنزعهما؟‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟!‬
Do you really wanna fight alongside us?
‫أستقاتل في صفنا حقًّا؟‬
If you come with me, I'll be kicking Kaido's ass right in front of you!
‫فأنا سأبطش بكايدو أمام ناظريك‬
I wish I could do it myself!
‫أرغب في هذا أيضًا‬
I've lost count of the beatings he's given me since I was a child!
‫عدد المرات التي بطش بي فيها منذ صغري لا تُعدّ ولا تُحصى‬
Every time I challenged him, I was defeated!
‫وأُهزم دومًا ما إن أتحداه‬
I see.
‫هكذا إذًا، فهمت، سأنزعهما من أجلك‬
Take them off?
‫تنزعهما؟‬
They've restricted my freedom for twenty years...
‫قيَّدا حُريَّتي طوال عشرين سنة...‬
It's not as easy as...
‫نزعمها ليس سهلًا...‬
It's been two years since the Summit War against Whitebeard!
‫مر عامان منذ حرب القمة التي قادها اللحية البيضاء‬
It's footage from the Performance Floor!
‫تُبث لقطات من طابق العرض المباشر‬
The gears of the world are turning once again!
‫بدأ العالم بالتحرك أخيرًا‬
The abolition of the Seven Warlords wasn't some act of madness by the government!
‫لم تفقد الحكومة رشدها حين قرروا إلغاء نظام الشيتشيبوكاي،‬
It's a sign of confidence in their ability
‫هذا دليل دامغ على ثقة مقر البحرية في قدرة «قواته الجديدة» على قمعنا‬
But while the World Government wallows in ignorance,
‫وبأخذ الحسبان بقناعة حكومة العالم المبالغ فيها،‬
we will gather the most powerful forces in this world...
‫سنجمع أشد القوى بطشًا في هذا العالم...‬
the ancient weapons!
‫الأسلحة العتيقة...!‬
To accomplish that...
‫ومن أجل هذا، نحن...‬
we have entered into an alliance with Big Mom!
‫تحالفنا مع بيغ مام...‬
Did I hear you...
‫هل أنا...‬
Olin the Oiran Captain of the Big Mom Pirates Bounty: 4 Billion 388 Million Berries
‫الأويران أولين‬ ‫قبطان قراصنة بيغ مام‬ ‫المكافأة: أربعة مليارات و388 مليون بيري‬
call out my name, Kaido?
‫من ناديتَني يا كايدو؟‬
Oh, my...
‫عجبًا!‬
Big Mom?!
‫بيغ مام!‬
Welcome back, Zeus.
‫عودًا حميدًا يا زيوس!‬
Ma... ma...
‫ما... ما...‬
Mama!
‫ماما!‬
She's terrifying up close!
‫لمرعبةٌ هي عن قرب!‬
She's the world's strongest old hag!
‫إنها أقوى عجوز في العالم!‬
Zeus!
‫زيوس!‬
Nami!
‫نامي!‬
They were caught?!
‫أقُبض عليهم؟!‬
You're finally here, Linlin!
‫أتيتِ أخيرًا يا لينلين!‬
What took you so long?!
‫ما الذي أخَّركِ؟‬
Don't be such a stickler, Kaido!
‫لا تتذمر يا كايدو‬
I made it in time.
‫ألم أصل في الوقت المناسب؟‬
As Kaido said,
‫كما كان يقول كايدو‬
we formed an alliance with a purpose in mind!
‫شكلنا تحالفًا لتحقيق غاية‬
A purpose?
‫غاية؟‬
If we're at each other's throats, it's out of our reach,
‫غايتنا صعبة المنال متفرقين،‬
but if we join hands, it's already within our grasp!
‫أما بترابطنا لتصير في قبضة يدنا!‬
Listen up, you louts!
‫أفهمتم؟‬
We're doubling down on piracy!
‫سنهتم أكثر بأعمال القرصنة!‬
At long last...
‫وأخيرًا...‬
...we're going to claim...
‫سنسعى خلف الكنز الأعظم...‬
...the great treasure One Piece!
‫ونظفر بكنز الون بيس...!‬
The One Piece...
‫الون بيس...‬
What the heck! That's my treasure!
‫إنه من نصيبي أنا!‬
Those jerks!
‫يا لهذين!‬
The fear of the ancient weapons...
‫وجود الأسلحة العتيقة...‬
will ignite a terrible war across the world!
‫سيوقع العالم في ويلات الحروب‬
Prepare yourselves!
‫جهزوا أنفسكم‬
That is the violent world that we desire!
‫فغايتنا تأسيس عالم عنفٍ مرير‬
How exciting!
‫هذا مشوق!‬
Any of you who serve Orochi, listen up!
‫لذا أنصتوا يا أتباع أوروتشي‬
You've got a choice to make.
‫عليكم الاختيار‬
A choice?
‫اختيار؟‬
This country...
‫هذه البلاد...‬
is a natural stronghold surrounded by the falls,
‫حصن يستعصي على حكومة العالم والبحرية اختراقه بسبب الشلالات التي تحوطه...‬
If we build more weapons factories...
‫إن بنينا مصانع أسلحة أكثر،‬
and force even the people of the Flower Capital to work,
‫وسخرنا سكان عاصمة الزهور للعمل بها،‬
this place will become a lawless land, a paradise for pirates!
‫سيصبح هذا المكان مرتعًا بلا قانون يحميه، ويغدو ملاذًا للقراصنة‬
Hey...
‫مهلًا...‬
Kaido, you swine!
‫أيها الوغد كايدو!‬
The Flower Capital is my territory!
‫إن عاصمة الزهور تحت سيطرتي!‬
Do you hear me?!
‫أتنصت أيها الوغد؟‬
For torturing the Kurozumi Clan, I'll bring those Kozuki devils to their knees
‫سأجعل شياطين عشيرة الكوزكي الذين عذبوا عشيرة الكوروزومي يجثون على ركبهم،‬
and subject them to all manner of horrors to keep them from rising up!
‫ولأبثّ في قلوبهم الرعب لمنعهم من التمرد ضدي‬
Forever and ever!
‫إلى أبد الآبدين...‬
Wano is mine to destroy!
‫ستخرب بلاد وانو على يداي‬
This country belongs to me!
‫هذه بلادي أنا!‬
Know your place, Kaido!
‫اعرف مقامك يا كايدو!‬
You're not even from here!
‫لا شأن لصعلوك مثلك بالبلاد!‬
Who do you think is making it possible for you to procure weapons?!
‫من وفر لك كل تلك الأسلحة برأيك؟‬
Wano can only exist with me!
‫بلاد وانو باقية بمشيئتي، أتعي ذلك؟‬
I see you understand.
‫أراك استوعبت‬
What we've got to do now...
‫ما علينا فعله أولًا...‬
is kill that brat immedia–
‫علينا قتل ذاك الشقي...‬
I don't care!
‫لا أهتم‬
We don't need him anymore!
‫لا حاجة لنا فيه بعد الآن‬
Utter tripe!
‫يا للهراء!‬
To me...
‫بالنسبة إلي...‬
both the Kurozumi Clan...
‫عشيرة الكوروزومي...‬
and the Kozuki Clan...
‫وعشيرة الكوزكي...‬
mean nothing!
‫لا قيمة لهما!‬
Momo!
‫مومو!‬
Hey, that's Momo!
‫مهلًا، أليس ذاك مومو؟!‬
Momo, wait for me!
‫تريّث يا مومو!‬
Hey, keep it down!
‫مهلًا، أخفض صوتك‬
Hey, what the hell?!
‫مهلًا، ماذا جرى؟‬
And now the pirate-loving fly is dead.
‫هلكت الذبابة التي كانت عالقة بالقراصنة‬
Those loyal to Orochi have five seconds to decide!
‫قرروا في غضون خمس ثوانٍ يا أتباع أوروتشي!‬
Become pirates and follow me...
‫إما أن تكونوا بصفنا نحن القراصنة،‬
or challenge us right here and die?
‫أم مواجهتنا والموت ها هنا‬
To prepare for the coming worldwide war,
‫من أجل إعداد العدة للحرب العالمية القادمة،‬
I will turn this country into a pirate empire!
‫سأُحوِّل هذه البلاد إلى إمبراطورية قراصنة!‬
We'll ramp up the expeditions for our primary business.
‫سنخرج في رحلات استكشافية أكثر لتعزيز تجارتنا الأولية،‬
So tonight,
‫وفي ليلتنا هذه،‬
we will relocate Onigashima to the Flower Capital,
‫سننقل أونيغاشيما إلى عاصمة الزهور،‬
and Wano will fall!
‫وستسقط بلاد وانو‬
That bastard!
‫ذلك الوغد!‬
The country's name will be New Onigashima!
‫سنغير هذه البلاد إلى «أونيغاشيما الجديدة»‬
And the new shogun will be my son...
‫والشوغن سيكون ابني...‬
Yamato!
‫ياماتو!‬
What did he...
‫ماذا...‬
just say?!
‫قال توًّا؟‬
You can't just force that on me!
‫لن تجبرني على هذا...‬
You shitty old man!
‫أيها الأب اللعين...!‬
Hurry up!
‫أسرعي!‬
They're gonna kill Momo!
‫سيُقتل مومو‬
I know a shortcut!
‫حسنٌ، لنختصر الطريق‬
Okay!
‫نعم!‬